A boy has two pets, one is a frog that lived in a tall jar and the other one is a dog, like a sausage dog.
The dog and the boy looked at the frog. The dog was excited about the frog, it was an excitable dog.
The boy got into bed and pulled the blankets up, while his dog slept on his bed.
The frog quieted down, got out of the jar and was soon gone.
Next day in the morning, the boy woke up and was surprised to see that the frog had disappeared.
He was shocked, looked for and started to unfold his clothes.
He asked himself, where was the frog, whilst continuing to unfold his clothes.
The dog went searching, put its head in the jar, straightened it and turned its head from side to side.
The boy looked through the window and rested his hands on the windowsill.
The dog sitting on the windowsill, moved its head from side to side, crouched and fell to the ground, smashing and scattering glass.
The boy was grumpy but he patted the dog.
The boy and the dog started searching for the frog, walked in the woods and yelled, "Where is the frog?" several times.
As they walked, they saw a burrow and the boy took a closer look at it.
The dog looked and barked at bees as they swarmed near their dome-shaped hive.
When it continued to bark, a rodent from the burrow bit the boy's nose.
The boy rubbed his nose and walked away from the burrow.
The dog barked and after the boy checked it out, climbed up the tree. An owl attacked him by surprise, passing his head.
The dog was aware of the fact that the bees had became irritated, so it ran away from them, as they swarmed.
The boy sprinted away as the owl flew and chased him. He climbed up, landed and sat down.
When he climbed up a big rock, his dog had disappeared.
The boy held on to something like some branches as the dog came back again.
Suddenly, the boy tightened his grip on "the branches" and realised "the branches" were deer antlers.
The deer ran as he lay on its head.
The dog ran next to the deer and barked, as the deer concentrated on walking quickly.
When the deer stood at the lip of a short-steep drop and threw the boy, he fell down.
Immediately he lay on the deer, he fell into water. The dog also did this.
The boy heard something, peeped and had a look around a log.
He pushed at the log and saw a loving couple of frogs, sitting romantically next to each other and embracing.
The boy leaned foward and was dazzled to see baby frogs sitting in a line.
He took one of the baby frogs whose parents embraced, indicating they wanted to stay.
The baby frog's father let him go with the boy and he carried it as he walked home.