This story is about a boy who is sleeping...
No, first he puts a frog into a big glass jar.
The dogs hops into the bed and they sleep.
When he wakes up the next morning, the frog is gone!
He looks around for the frog. He shakes out all his socks, but doesn't find the frog.
The dog wants to help look, but he sticks his head right in the glass jar, and gets stuck, the poor thing.
The boy is still looking around, when he sees the open window. He opens it and calls out for the frog.
But the dog falls out of the window, and manages to break the jar off of his head.
Finally, as the jar hits the ground, the glass breaks.
So the boy keeps searching for the frog, high and low, calling out for the frog, but it's disappeared.
As he's looking, he gets an idea. There's a tree with a hole in its trunk nearby.
The boy climbs up to it and peers in. But an angry owl bursts out and scares him. He thought the frog might be there, but it isn't.
And then he gets chased by bees. There he is running along, a whole cloud of bees behind him.
So he's going along, searching, and he comes across a big rock.
The boy climbs up onto this rock, and then he looks down and realises that it's actually a deer, from the other side it's a deer, and the boy is sitting on it. The deer takes of running.
The deer runs, and then bucks the boy off its back, he can't do anything, and over a drop into a pond.
And the dog jumps into the water too.
And then they see a big log near the pond.
They think the frog must be in there, and sneak up quietly.
They peer around the log and see that the frog has a whole row of baby frogs!
INDECIPHERABLE
Well, in the log they found, in the water, were more just-born baby frogs.