There's a little boy alseep in his bed.
He has a pet frog in a jar at the foot of his bed. The frog escapes.
The boy also has a dog.
The boy and his dog search for... no, sorry. The boy gets dressed and at the same time his dog gets its head stuck in the jar.
The boy cried out to his frog through the window. Subsequently his dog fell out the window and onto the ground below, smashing the glass jar.
Luckily, the dog can still walk.
They make their way down a slope and come across a hilly park.
The boy finds a hole in the ground and thinks that his frog might have gone down there. He yells into the hole.
At the same time his dog is taunting a beehive, him/there.
The animal that actually lives in the hole springs up and sbites the boy on his nose. This startles the little boy.
Meanwhile, the bees became agitated with the dog.
The boy ignores his dog and instead walks OVER to a tree with a hole in it.
The boy thinks his frog might be in there so he has a look in the hole. Instead, an angry owl appears fluttering its wings. The boy realises he was wrong..
At the same time, the beehive collapses and splatters onto the ground. Then the bees chase the dog until he finds refuge on a rock.
The boy joins his dog on top of the rock. He holds on to some branches that appear in front of him and cries out to his frog. His frog has to be out there somewhere.
The boy soon realises that he is holding on to deer antlers. The deer becomes angry and as he gets to his feet, he scoups up the boy onto his head. The boy is stuck and forced to ride on the deer.
The dog also rides on the deer.
The deer becomes frustrated and throws the boy and his dog from his head by bucking. The boy and his dog plummet into water.
While in the water, the boy and his frog... sorry I meant dog, heard a noise coming from behind a log.
They creep towards the log quietly and look behind it. There he finds his frog with a partner and several baby frogs sitting around them.
The boy decides to leave them alone. He says good bye and leaves.