This is a story about a boy who was in his bedroom and he had a frog which he kept in a stoppered jar.
The boy also had a dog. They both enjoyed looking at the frog. Good, that's settled.
Immediately, they both got on the bed, lay on it and slept.
The boy snored as the frog escaped from the jar.
Next day in the morning, the boy checked to see if the frog was still in the jar.
The boy and his dog were disappointed when they realised that the frog had disappeared.
The boy looked out through the window, looking for frog and wondered where it was.
The dog with a jar stuck on its head, jumped up to the windowsill and fell to the ground.
When the jar shattered on the ground, the boy quickly got out of the window.
The boy put on his shoes, but before putting them on, he checked inside the shoes as he thought the frog, might have been inside but there was nothing there.
He put them on.
After a short walk and hunt around, he sighted a wooded vast flandland at the back of the house, which described athe nearby hillside.
He yelled whilst the dog looked at the outlined bands of a dome-shaped honey beehive, which was hanging in the tree.
The dog walked to the tree with the hive and the bees swarmed out.
When the boy was looking around he saw a burrow, which he thought the frog might have been in it, so he took a closer look.
A rodent (the narrator thinks it is squirrel) got out of the burrow and the boy smelt it break wind, so he got away and went OVER there.
The boy saw one big tree trunk with a hole which he thought the frog was in, but when he took a close look at it, an owl got out and attacked him.
Um, the dog was still near the beehive and when it played around with the bees, the hive fell to the ground and the bees swarmed out.
The boy walked impatiently as the bird flapped its wings and flew at the boy who shooed it away.
He walked to an area which had a big dome-shaped rock with "branches" and a small rock in front.
The boy climbed up the rocks and so did the dog. When he held on to the "branches", he was surprised to see that they were actually deer's antlers.
After the boy got onto the deer, it stood up and ran.
The boy said to the dog, "Follow me", and the dog followed him running.