There's a little boy who catches a frog, and he puts it in a big jar.
Him and his dog peer down at it for a little while, and then hop into bed and go to sleep.
The next day when they wake up, the frog is gone!
They look everywhere in the room, turning things OVER looking inside his shoes.
The boy sees the window, and starts calling out for the frog.
But the dog wants to help, and sticks his head inside the jar.
Then, with the jar still on his head, he hops up on the window sill with the boy, only he falls out and smashes the jar.
The boy picks him up and comforts him.
Then the both of them set off into the forest, calling out and looking high and low for the frog.
The boy sees a hole in the ground. He looks down it, and a beaver jumps out of it and hits him on the nose.
Nearby, the dog is barking up a tree at some bees. Of course it goes wrong, the beehive falls to the ground and the bees start chasing the dog.
And the boy, he climbs up a tree and looks in a hollow. But there's an owl in there, that flies out and surprises him, so he falls out of the tree.
The two of them keep going, calling everywhere for the frog.
So . . . The owl chases the boy, and he runs up onto a large rock. He grabs these branches sticking up behind the rock and looks around.
But he gets a shock when he realises he's actually holding onto a deer!
The deer takes off running, with the boy hanging onto it's antlers and his dog trying to keep up, running along side.
Then the deer throws the boy off his antlers and into a pond, with his dog too.
Suddenly they both catch a sound. It's the noise of a frog calling that they hear!
They sneak OVER to this big log, and look OVER it . . . There's the frog! Well, a mother and a father frog with nine little children.
Cute little things.
And. . . the mother frog, well one of the frogs, I don't know whether the boy caught the mother or the father frog, one of the frogs gives the boy one of the baby frogs. The frogs say goodbye, and the boy heads home carrying a new baby frog.